C'mon, Bonfire, hurry up and free me.
I can't exactly eat toast
with my hands tied behind my back.
Are you sure it was a good idea
bringing him with us, Teach?
He's the only one who knows
what Purple Ant looks like.
Unfortunately, that makes him valuable.
Thanks kindly.
I have a question for you.
Do you remember Olivia?
Huh? Of course I do.
Tell me, did you love her?
Oh, for sure.
All I had to do was whisper
sweet nothings in her ear,
and that pawn of a woman was
willing to risk her life for-
Grete?
I apologize.
Thea...
Would you be able to peer into that man's heart?
The sooner we get that intel out of him,
the sooner we can give him a pair of cement shoes.
I never expected that he would rile you up so much.
I understand how you feel, but I can't.
Every time I try to look him in the eye,
he puts his guard up.
We can just leave him as-is for the time being.
From what I've found,
there's been a string of murders,
suspicious deaths, and disappearances
taking place in secret here in Mitario.
The vast majority of the victims were
intelligence operatives
who got involved with
the Tolfa Economic Conference.
The murder methods cover the spectrum.
There have been stabbings, strangulations,
vehicular assaults made to look like suicides,
and accidents...
And you think that the Galgad Empire's
Serpent team is behind it all, Boss?
It wouldn't surprise me if they had someone
capable of pulling that off.
They're killing off enemy spies
and shifting things in the Empire's favor.
I want you all to continue approaching
conference attendees and gathering intel.
Very well.
Our ultimate goal for this mission
is to capture Purple Ant,
the Serpent member who's infiltrated the city.
I'm going to be operating independently
and interrogating anyone who seems shady.
All that said, make sure you don't take
any unnecessary risks.
Remember, we're up against the people who
managed to bring the legendary Inferno team low.
Understood.
My eyes were opened up wide
By a scene that rent my heart
See it flitting, flitting through the gaps in your fingers
Stare at the truth as it comes into view
Is what's been built here paradise?
Tumbling down head over heels
Oh, I know this might be a wasteland
But I have to land so I can survive on my own
I have to go now
I vomited up magificent blood
That these flowers I planted here might bloom eternal
I love this hopeless world enough to give
All that my lungs and my legs and my hands have to give for it
And I swear I'll find a dream
That was worth all this sorrow
MISSION: Dreamspeaker II
Goodness me, you really saved my bacon there.
Please, don't hold back.
Order as much as you want.
For real?
In that case, let's start out...
with one of everything from here to here!
It's no wonder you're VP of one of the
leading tea manufacturers in the Bumal Kingdom.
You've got a big heart!
Thanks for this, and for agreeing to
give me an exclusive interview.
Oh, it's my pleasure.
Still, I can't believe someone stole my briefcase
right out of that coffee shop.
Who knows where I'd be
if you hadn't gallantly retrieved it!
It's a shame they never caught whoever did it.
Details, details.
More importantly, you are going to
publish that article, right?
I've given interviews to a number of reporters,
but none of them ever make it to print.
Oh, really?
I guess I'm just unlucky.
I don't know why, but none of
the reporters even return my calls.
How rude is that?
By the way, who's your friend?
Oh, that's Barron.
They were supposed to send a chauffeur
out from the motherland,
but he came down with food poisoning.
I had to find a local replacement in a hurry.
Oui.
He might look scary, but he's good at what he does.
You told me you were a middleweight boxer
up until a few years ago, right?
Oui, I had to retire when I tore my ligament.
Ah, thank you.
Oui.
And where is it you're taking me, Miranda?
Don’t worry, I think you'll like it.
You're trying to make friends
with deep pockets, right?
This place has enough fat cats
to make your head spin.
An underground casino, huh?
What's a college student like you doing
hanging around somewhere this sketchy?
My uncle's a regular.
He brought me here once, and I got hooked.
A dart?
This place is pretty exclusive.
It'll help grease the wheels if you play a round
before I start introducing you around.
Do you know the rules?
It's easy.
You throw three darts a round,
and we take turns and compete on score.
When you throw them, you want to do it like this.
By the way, that spot I just hit was the triple 20.
It's the most valuable spot on the board.
So, like this?
I can't believe it.
Nice throws.
Wow, you're really something.
You were right, this is easy.
Well, I don't plan on losing.
Wouldn't have it any other way.
How are they doing that?
So, how do you know who wins?
Normally, it ends after eight rounds.
And what if it's a tie?
There's a special rule
where you play overtime rounds.
Who designed this dumb game?
We'll be here for the rest of our lives.
Well, guess we gotta keep going.
I wouldn't rack up too many points if I were you.
Why's that?
Down here, we play for keeps.
If you lose, you have to pay the winner
a hundred donnies for every point they got.
You're awful, Miranda.
You never told me we were gambling.
If I lose, I'll owe you more than the average person
in this country makes in four years.
There's no way I could pay that much.
You're welcome to pay with your body.
This place runs strip shows.
They're pretty nasty.
The performers get dissected...
with a big old guillotine.
I'll never understand the stuff rich people are into.
Lillian, you've got some guests.
They say they've got a few questions for you.
They're waiting out back.
I'll get right on it.
I dunno why, but I'm getting bad vibes.
I guess all that experience has
awakened my spy instincts.
Whoever's looking for me is an enemy.
I'm sure of it!
No worries, though.
I'll just use the techniques Teach taught me
to turn the tables on 'em!
Are you all right?
I think I drank too much.
Where's the VP?
Oui.
He and his secretary left for another bar.
He asked me to give you a ride home.
I really 'ppreciate it.
Oops...
Sorry.
Don't worry about it.
I'll go get you some water.
You lookin' for these?
Sleeping pills.
The VP didn't put you up to this.
Who're you working for?
Hey, get back here!
Looks like the story about the
torn ligament was bullshit.
You're not goin' anywhere!
He blocked the entrance?!
Oui.
Shit, he lured me here on purpose.
What is this place?
I've trained to be able to fight
without needing to see.
Is this guy the spy killer they warned me about?!
This prison of darkness will be your grave.
They look like they mean business.
You looking for me?
I'll give you credit.
It was pretty sporting of you to come at me head-on.
Hello there.
We're with the Mitario Police Department.
Oh, I get it.
Coming as cops was a bold move.
Did you really think those disguises would fool me?
Disguises?
What are you talking about?
Wait, you're actual cops?
Long story short, you're a suspect in a murder case.
Two people were shot to death the night before last.
There's an eyewitness who puts you there,
and we have a warrant.
No, wait...
Th-this is a frame job!
A Galgad spy's trying to set me up!
And why would a spy go after some random
exchange student who works at a burger joint?
What's their motive?
Um, well...
This, uh, this isn't what it looks like!
Lillian Hepburn, you're under arrest
for suspected murder.
U-under arrest?!
I hate to break it to you,
but you're not the first prodigy I've run across.
It's rare, but it happens.
But even for prodigies who can throw
perfect games like it's nothing,
their composure crumbles in an instant
when their lives are on the line.
I wonder how long you'll be able to keep your cool
now that you know the truth?
Look at it the other way round.
If I win, it'll mean you served yourself
up on a silver platter for me.
Makes my job real easy.
Who hired you?
Once I beat you, I'll make you sing like a bird.
Could you not write me off so easily?
Its trajectory shifted?
How embarrassing.
And after you talked such a big game.
Take a good, long look.
This is the moment your whole life ends.
MISSION: Dreamspeaker II
They're late.
Why aren't they reporting in
like they're supposed to?
What happened, do you think?
That's a good question.
The most likely answer is that
they've been caught by surprise.
We all share a common weakness,
so I'm a little bit concerned.
What weakness is that?
We do all our training by going after the boss.
In other words, we practice attacking,
but we're not used to having to defend ourselves.
I'm sure it will be fine, though.
I've prepared measures for just such an eventuality.
A small spy can make a big difference.
Because if there's one time where we truly shine...
How unlucky.
What're you talkin' about, unlucky?
That was perfect.
Oui.
Backup, hm?
Tough luck, man.
As soon as we survived your first attack,
your defeat was already sealed.
If there's one time where we truly shine...
it's when we go on the offensive.
This is all an Imperial spy's conspiracy!
I'm being set up!
Is she still going on about that?
Hm? What's with the stuffed animal on your back?
Wh-what's going on?!
It's a stun gun?
Does that mean-
Yo, Sis, we gotta book it!
Annette!
She missed.
That's a single 20!
Th-there was a mouse!
It threw itself against my ankle!
Seriously?
Who cares, lady?
That's a pretty sad excuse.
I threw my dart perfectly.
So, why?
Come on, it's your turn.
The AC unit?
It's only blowing when I take my turn.
What's wrong?
Lost your nerve?
Gosh, I hope your darts don't go
flying the wrong way again.
So, it was you.
Who, me?
Let me tell you a secret.
Down here, all that matters is where your darts land.
Well, don't you worry about me.
I already have a solution.
Oh, it worked.
Did you seriously just...
I lived here in the States for a bit during the war.
Around these parts,
you call that a windup pitch, right?
There's no way you can keep pulling off flukes like-
Nice.
Hey, what's going on?
What's everyone watching?
At this rate, we'll never be done.
What do you say we start throwing
all three darts at once?
Have you lost it?
What, too chicken?
It's easy.
I'm here to play darts, not perform stunts.
What're you doing?
Coward!
Throw all three!
Do it! Do it!
Live a little!
She's distracted.
Hurry it up!
Why the surprised face?
Did you think you'd won?
It's no use.
Nothing you do can shake me.
That's the stuff, right there!
I've put in the hours.
I've thrown tens, hundreds of thousands of darts.
You're saying that's the difference between us?
That's right.
And it's why I don't get tired.
Whoa!
The reason you keep doing that
three-at-once stunt
is to bring down the total number of throws
you have to make.
That stance you're taking
puts a lot of strain on your arm.
Sooner or later, you'll mess up.
Not even prodigies are immune to fatigue.
You're in the same boat, no?
Didn't I just tell you?
I don't get tired.
Someone like you would never understand.
You have no idea just how long I've spent
honing my technique.
I could throw a thousand darts and never miss once.
Why go that far?
Because of the pain.
The what?
There's a man whispering in my head.
"Keep training," he says.
And if I defy him, the pain comes back.
It's agony.
And that's why...
I believe.
That if I work hard enough,
I'll be able to overcome any adversity!
Can you say the same?
Your arm doesn't look like it can take much more.
Going back to throwing them one at a time?
Won't that just increase the
number of throws you have to make?
That's only one point.
I guess that settles it.
You finally hit your limit.
Hold on, I've still got one dart left.
It won't change a thing.
You failed to overcome me.
I love moments like these.
It always feels wonderful to have
hard work outdo raw talent.
Miss Monika, you need to run!
On its own, hard work isn't worth jack.
You've trained hard, sure.
But that alone isn't enough.
What are you babbling about?
You piss me off.
You, and your shitty value system.
"Hard work is enough to overcome any adversity"?
How many people do you think die in
this world awash in pain of ours
just because they were born in the wrong place
or without enough talent?
Remember this.
In our world, people without fire in their hearts
are nothing more than garbage.
There are walls.
Walls that no amount of hard work
will ever let you scale.
It's infuriating, the way you pretend to be a nobody
when you're just as talented yourself.
Are you done making pointless speeches?
This is game, set, and match.
You want to know why you lost?
It's your talent you should have trusted in,
not your hard work.
That's 121 to 120.
The win's mine.
Y-you think this is a joke?!
You cheated!
We all saw it!
Remember what you just said?
"Down here, all that matters is where your darts land."
All told, that's 890,100 donnies you owe me.
It'd take most people twenty years to earn that much.
If you can't pay, I'd be happy to spot you.
All I'd ask for in return is intel
on the person who hired-
Where's my gratitude?
Th-thank you, sir.
Allow me to introduce you.
This here is my pet dog.
Up until five years ago,
he was a med student at Mitario University.
They called him a boy genius,
and his grades were outstanding.
Now, though, he's nothing more than a mangy mutt.
And it's all because of this.
I have a gift.
All my life, I've known.
I've known what kind of pain will chisel fear
deep into people's minds.
Give me a week with anyone,
and I can make them fall in line.
If I order them to die, then that's what they'll do.
The pain I offer rewrites people's brains.
It isn't logic that makes them obey me.
It's their primal instincts.
Students, martial artists,
police officers, bank workers,
actresses, and killers alike
prostrate themselves before their king.
They spend their days
blending in with ordinary society.
By night, though, they hone
their assassination techniques for me
like men and women possessed.
You and your friends didn't stand a chance.
They hunt down spies
for as long as they draw breath,
and when they fail, they kill themselves on the spot.
That's how my Worker Ants operate.
Ah, standing on one leg and feeling the pain
I've shared it with you, are you getting this vertigo?
I've got love, but that's not what's washing over me
I spring up, I spring up, I'm a nuisance and I'm in the way
Am I "really okay"?
What good will asking that do?
Just praise me and be on your way
Blame it on a mirror that's unspeakable, unhealable
A sullied life that's unseeable, unfading
Tear right on through and see through lies with frigid eyes
An innocent item that's unbeatable, unbuyable
It's an undiscarded corpse, after all
Fight back naked with your unconcealed resolve in hand
(whoo, whoo, ooh)
A wishy-washy destiny all covered in graffiti
Recklessly deceiving even God